{
    "data": {
        "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Which river separates Cornwall from Devon?",
                "answer": "The Tamar"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which island group includes Ibiza, Menorca and Majorca?",
                "answer": "The Balearics Islands"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the motorways called in France?",
                "answer": "Autoroutes"
            },
            {
                "question": "The New Shekel is the currency of which country?",
                "answer": "Israel"
            },
            {
                "question": "Mosul, Arbil and Basra are among the principal cities in which country?",
                "answer": "Iraq"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which capital city has a name that means 'good airs' in English?",
                "answer": "Buenos Aires"
            },                         
            {
                "question": "In which county is the historic Bluebell Railway to be found?",
                "answer": "Sussex (in both East and West)"
            },                       
            {
                "question": "Zanzibar and Pemba Islands are part of which country?",
                "answer": "Tanzania"
            },              
            {
                "question": "In which county is the bracing Skegness located?",
                "answer": "Lincolnshire"
            },              
            {
                "question": "In which Irish county is the Malin Head, the most northerly point of the Irish mainland?",
                "answer": "Donegal"
            },                        
            {
                "question": "If all traditional English counties were listed alphabetically, which would come first?",
                "answer": "Bedfordshire"
            },             
            {
                "question": "The Tay Bridge runs south from which city?",
                "answer": "Dundee"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which two countries lie on the island of Hispaniola?",
                "answer": "Haiti and the Dominican Republic"
            },             
            {
                "question": "The ancient city of Machu Picchu is in which country?",
                "answer": "Peru"
            },              
            {
                "question": "What is Britain's most southerly National Park?",
                "answer": "Dartmoor"
            },             
            {
                "question": "What alternative name is given to the River Thames as it passes through Oxford?",
                "answer": "The Isis"
            },     
            {
                "question": "The Ross and Weddell Seas lap the shores of which continent?",
                "answer": "Antartica"
            },               
            {
                "question": "Piraeus serves as the ort for which major city?",
                "answer": "Athens"
            },             
            {
                "question": "What is the capital of the Falkland Islands?",
                "answer": "Port Stanley"
            },             
            {
                "question": "On which canal can the Gatun and Miraflores Locks be found?",
                "answer": "The Panama Canal"
            },               
            {
                "question": "Brunei is one of the three countries which share which island, the third largest in the world?",
                "answer": "Borneo"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which national flag is the only one in the world to be a single colour with no design and insignia on it?",
                "answer": "Libya"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country are the Angel Falls, the world's highest waterfall?",
                "answer": "Venezuela"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which federal state contains 26 Cantons?",
                "answer": "Switzerland"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country is Liberation of Saigon Day on April 30, a public holiday?",
                "answer": "Vietnam"
            },   
            {
                "question": "Mauritius is found in which ocean?",
                "answer": "The Indian Ocean"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which is the smallest and southernmost region of mainland Portugal, known primarily for tourism?",
                "answer": "Algarve"
            },         
            {
                "question": "Dulles Internation Airport serves which American city?",
                "answer": "Washington D.C."
            },       
            {
                "question": "Which is Britain's busiest railway station in terms of services, with more than 2,000 trains a day passing through?",
                "answer": "Clapham Junction"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which island is separated from the British mainland by the Menai Straits?",
                "answer": "Anglesey"
            },            
            {
                "question": "LOT is the national airline if which country?",
                "answer": "Poland"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country are the Great Bear Lake and the Great Slave Lake?",
                "answer": "Canada"
            },            
            {
                "question": "On which Caribbean island can you find the Blue Mountains?",
                "answer": "Jamaica"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country is the port of Fray Bentos?",
                "answer": "Uruguay"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which inlet of the Irish Sea separates Cumbria from Dumfries and Galloway?",
                "answer": "The Solway Firth"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which line of latitude is at 66Â°33' N?",
                "answer": "Arctic Circle"
            },            
            {
                "question": "The Torres Strait separates Australia from which island?",
                "answer": "New Guinea"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country is the legendary city of Timbuktu?",
                "answer": "Mali"
            },            
            {
                "question": "From which east coast port in the UK can you get ferries to Hook of Holland and Esbjerg?",
                "answer": "Harwich"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country are the mysterious Nazca lines to be found?",
                "answer": "Peru"
            },            
            {
                "question": "St Davids, St Thomas and St James Park are all railway stations in which English city?",
                "answer": "Exeter"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which country is the Province of Lapland to be found?",
                "answer": "Finland"
            },            
            {
                "question": "What term is given to a territory which is part of a country but is surrounded by other countries so it is physically separate from the rest of the country?",
                "answer": "An exclave"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Clearwell Caves and the viewpoint of Symmonds Yat are located on the edge of which forest?",
                "answer": "The Forest of Dean"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which Costa lies on the Spanish coast north of Barcelona?",
                "answer": "The Costa Brava"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which island in the South Atlantic is named after the Portuguese navigator who first sighted it in 1506?",
                "answer": "Tristan da Cunha"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Tashkent is the capital of which one of the Asian 'stans'?",
                "answer": "Uzbekistan"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In which British island group are the Hoy, Westray, North Ronaldsay and South Ronaldsay to be found?",
                "answer": "The Orkney Islands"
            },            
            {
                "question": "On which island is Ronaldsway airport?",
                "answer": "Isle of Man"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which is the only lake in Scotland to be acutally called a lake?",
                "answer": "The Lake of Menteith"
            },            
            {
                "question": "On which river are the Victoria Falls to be found?",
                "answer": "The Zambezi"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which landlocked sea is 422m (1385 ft) below sea level?",
                "answer": "The Dead Sea"
            },            
            {
                "question": "In terms of population and actual city size, what is France's second largest city?",
                "answer": "Marseilles"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which country's flag includes a cedar tree?",
                "answer": "Lebanon"
            },            
            {
                "question": "The Spanish Steps are found in which city?",
                "answer": "Rome"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which river, which enters the Atlantic at Oporto, is the centre of the making of Port?",
                "answer": "The Douro"
            },            
            {
                "question": "The 886-metre (2,907 ft) high Pen y Fan is the highest point in which range of hills?",
                "answer": "The Brecon Beacons"
            },            
            {
                "question": "O'Hare Airport is one of the busiest in the world. Which American city does it serve?",
                "answer": "Chicago"
            },            
            {
                "question": "The Storting is the parliament of which country?",
                "answer": "Norway"
            },            
            {
                "question": "Which island lies between the Kintyre peninsula and Ayrshire?",
                "answer": "Arran"
            }            
        ]
    }
}